http://www.machines4wood.com/privacy-policy

30 th Nov COVID 19 Update : Showroom Open by Appointment Only. Dispatch + ‘phones as Normal
Menu
New Machinery
New MachineryScott+Sargeant has a long and rich history supplying woodworking machinery to trade workshops and industry - having developed into a leading specialist supplier of woodworking machines.Aluminium Machinery
Aluminium Composite Panel MachinesAluminium Cutting MachinesAssembly
Hoffman Jointers and Dovetail Jointing SystemWood WelderClamping MachinesCNC RoutersCombination MachinesCompressorsDovetailersDrilling MachinesDust Extractors & Waste
Briquetting MachinesDust Extractors
Enclosed Dust ExtractorsDust Extractor TablesDust Extractor BoothsDust Extractor SystemsDust Extractor PlantsFine Dust ExtractorsDust Extractor Bag SystemsHoggers & ShreddersRecycling MachinesWoodburners & HeatersFume ExtractorsEdgebandersEducation MachinesFinishing & Spraying
Coating MachinesDrying EquipmentSpray BoothsBrushing MachinesGlue SpreadersGrinders & Toolroom
Bandsaw Blade WeldersMetalworking MachinesGuillotinesLaser Cutting & EngravingMorticersPlaners
Four Sided PlanersPlaner MouldersCombined Planer ThicknessersSurface PlanersThicknesser PlanersPower Feed UnitsPressing Machines
Bag Vacuum PressesCabinet PressesFrame PressesLaminating PressesMembrane PressesPlatten PressesVeneer PressesSolid Surface PressesRoutersPackaging & Wrapping MachinesPlastics Processing MachinesSanders
Disc SandersProfile SandersBrushing MachinesBelt Sanders
Wide Belt SandersNarrow Belt SandersDrum SandersSaws
Band ResawsBandsawsCrosscut SawsMultirip & Rip SawsPanel SawsSawmills & Portable SawmillsSite & Mitre SawsSpecialist SawsTable SawsWall & Vertical Panel SawsRadial Arm SawsSaw BenchesShreddersSingle Phase Woodworking MachinesSpecial Furniture MachinesSpecial OffersSpindle MouldersTenonersTimber Frame MachinesVeneer Machines
Veneer Cutting MachinesVeneer Joining MachinesVeneer PressesWood Drying KilnsVacuum Lifters
Lift Boards & PanelsLift BagsLift Cartons & BoxesLift BarrelsLifting WoodJib Cranes & GantriesWindow Making MachinesWood Lathes & Turning
Copy LathesHand LathesRod Milling MachinesWrapping MachinesUsed Machinery
Used MachineryScott+Sargeant has one of the largest used woodworking machinery showrooms in the whole of the UK and Europe. Browse our huge range of industrial, second-hand woodworking machine online or visit us today. We have great prices on used tools as well as a 1000s of spare parts, tools and accessories. Our range includes used CNC routers, edgebanding machines, panel saws, sanders and more. Leading manufacturers are represented in the used stock including, Altendorf, Brandt, Boere, Biesse, Balestrini, Bacci, Homag, Holzma, Martin, SCM, Sedgwick, Wadkin & Weeke.CNC Routers - UsedCombination Machines - UsedCompressors - UsedDovetailers - UsedDrilling Machines - UsedDust Extractors - UsedEdgebanders - UsedFinishing Equipment - UsedGrinders - UsedGuillotines - UsedLathes &Turning - UsedMiscellaneous - UsedMortise Machines - UsedMoulders - UsedPlaner Thicknessers - UsedPresses & Cramps - UsedRouters - UsedSanders - UsedSanders Wide Belt - UsedSaws - Used
Band Resaws - UsedBandsaws - UsedBeamsaws - UsedCrosscut Saws - UsedMultirip & Rip Saws - UsedPanel Saws - UsedRip Saws - UsedVertical Panel Saws - UsedSpindle Moulders - UsedSurface Planers - UsedTenoners - UsedThicknessers - UsedUsed Spares & ToolingCNC
CNC Router DepartmentCNC Machines, Tooling and parts for CNC Routers, CNC Lasers, CNC Tools, Spiral Router Cutters, Diamond Special tools, CNC Drill bits, Tool Holders, Vacuum pods, pumps vanes and vacuum cord with rapid delivery anywhere. Affordable prices + top quality. AccessoriesAggregatesColletsDrillsCNC RoutersCNC LasersTools HoldersSpiral CuttersCNC Router BitsDiamond BitsUsed CNC RoutersVacuum SparesTooling
Tooling for MachinesFind the widest range of tools, saw blades, and router bits for your Bandsaw, CNC Router, Moulder, Mortiser, Sliding Table Saw, Spindle Moulder or Tenoner. We also can make special tooling: custom  router cutters to order in TCT or PCD. Bandsaw Blades
Centauro Bandsaw BladesFelder Bandsaw BladesiTECH Bandsaw BladesRecord Bandsaw BladesStartrite Bandsaw BladesBushes+SleevesCircular Saw BladesCNC ToolsCNC ColletsCNC Tool Holders
Tool HoldersPull StudsSpanners for CNCBandsaw BladesCarbide Knives
Straight TC BladesShaped TC BladesCutter Heads
Adjustable GrooversBoxed Tool SetsDoor ToolsEdge Radius+ChamferGlue Joint ToolsGrooversPanel RaisersPlaner BlocksProfile BlocksRebate BlocksSerrated Limiter BlocksSerrated Moulder BlocksTenon BlocksTenoning DiscsTongue + Groove ToolsVariable Angle BlocksWindow Cill ToolsWindow ToolsWobble SawsDowel DrillsDrill AdaptorsDrills
Auger DrillsBushes for DrillsCNC Drill AdaptorsCNC Drill BitsCountersinksDowel DrillsDrills for WoodForstner + Cylinder Drill BitsHole SawsPlug CuttersRosette CuttersSpecial Drill BitsEdgebander ToolsFinger JointGlue Joint ToolsGrooversMortiser Tools
Mortise Chisel + Bits: ImperialMortise Chisel + Bits: MetricLock Mortise ToolsMortise Chains Bars + SprocketsOscillating Mortise ChiselsSlot Mortise CuttersPlaner Blades
Planer Blades - StandardBulldozer Planer BladesCentrofix Planer BladesCentrolock Planer BladesESTA Planer BladesKanefusa Planer BladesPortable Planer BladesSinus Planer BladesSpecial Planer BladesTerminus Planer BladesTERSA Planer BladesPlaner BlocksRouter Bits
Acrylic CuttersAluminium CuttersBarley TwistBullnose BitsCarving BitsCMT Sets of BitsCNC Router BitsCNC Lock BitsChamfer + BevelCompression Spiral BitsCove BitsDiamond Router BitsDovetail BitsDrawer + Finger PullFlush TrimmersGlue Joint BitsKeyhole BitsOgee BitsOvolo BitsPanel BitsTool HoldersProfile + Scribe SetsRadius BitsRaised Panel BitsRebate BitsReplacement Tip BitsSlotters + GrooversSpiral Router BitsSolid Surface BitsSpoilboard BitsT-Slot BitsTongue + Groove BitsTrimmers + Profile BitsV Groove + Engrave BitsWindow Router BitsThreaded Router BitsSanding HeadsSaw Blades
Bandsaw BladesCircular Saw Blades for WoodContractors SawbladesFestool Saw BladesHogging SawsMultirip Saw BladesNegative Rake Saw BladesNon Ferous Saw BladesPCD Diamond Saw BladesPlastics + Solid Surface BladesSaw BushesJigsaw BladesMulti Tool BladesHole SawsSerrated Back Tools
60 mm Serrated Profiles + Limiters80 mm Serrated Profiles + Limiters100 mm Serrated Profiles + LimitersSerrated Back BarSerrated Back BlocksSerrated Back KnivesSerrated Back Profiled CuttersSpacers + Shims
C SpannersReducing BushesSpare ScrewsSpacers + ShimsSpindle Moulder Tools + Cutters
Adjustable GrooversDoor ToolsEuro Limiter BlocksEuro Cutters 40mmEuro Cutters 50mmEuro Limiters 40mmEuro Limiters 50mmGlue Joint HeadsGrooversHandrail CuttersOMAS 394 CuttersRebate BlocksScribes & LimitersSerrated Cutter ProfilesWhitehill Cutters + LimitersWhitehill BlanksWhitehill Panel Raising CuttersWindow Tools & CuttersVariable Angle BlocksTenoning ToolsWide Bandsaw BladesAluminium CuttersCopy Lathes ToolsAccessories
Accessories + Spare Parts for MachinesWe can help you find spare parts for your traditional or CNC machines and machine breakdowns - we specialise in spares and service with daily despatches worldwide by courier. We can supply tooling and hard to find spare partsBandsaw AccessoriesBandsaw BladesCarriers + LiftersCircular Saw AccessoriesCircular Saw BladesClamps + CrampsCNC Router AggregatesCNC Router SpannersConsumablesCrosscut FencesDrive BeltsDrying Racks, Spray TablesDucting & AccessoriesEdgebander AccessoriesElectrical EquipmentExtension TablesFeed Rollers
Rubber Feed RollersSteel Feed RollersFiltersGlue ApplicatorsGuards For MachinesHandles + Knobs
Hand WheelsLocking HandlesHandling EquipmentJigs + GuidesMeasuring + SettingPlaner AccessoriesPowerfeed SparesPress SparesPush SticksRespiratorsRoller Tables + StandsSafety - GeneralSafety MatsSetting StandsSoftwareSpare Parts forStop SystemsSpindle Moulder AccessoriesTrack PadsVacuum ClampsVacuum Press BagsVacuum SparesWoodturning AccessoriesHand Tools
Hand ToolsBrowse our huge range of hand tools for your woodworking business. With decades of experience supplying the global market with quality machines, tools and accessories, we're sure to help you find the right woodworking tools you're looking for.Biscuit JointersCarpenters ToolsChisels - CarvingChisels - GeneralChisels - Woodturning
Bowl GougesScrapersSkew ChiselsClamps & CrampsDrillsDetail Sanders & Air ToolsEdge TrimmersExtractorsGrease & Oil GunsGrindersHand Profile SanderMitre SawsMortisers - PortablePlanesPortable EdgebandersPortable PlanersPortable SawsRouting Equipment
Router AccessoriesPortable RoutersRouter Accessories & JigsRouter TablesSanders
Orbit SandersSanders - FloorSpray GunsTackers & NailersVicesWork BenchesBy Brand
Market Leading BrandsAIgnerAtemagArdesiaBacciBesseyBrookhuisBrusaCamvacCasadei IndustriaCasatiCentauroCMTDMC SandersElesaFamag DrillsFlipStopForestor SawmillsHarwiHitecoHoffmanInnovatorKa-Ma SprayingFamag DrillsHoffmanItalpresseiTECH
CNC RoutersDust ExtractorsBandsawsCombination MachinesCNC AccessoriesCrosscut SawsEdgebandersPanel SawsPlanersPowerfeedsSandersSpindle MouldersTable SawsWorkshop AccessoriesKlueberLamelloManut LMMartin
Martin Panel SawsMartin PlanersMartin Spindle MouldersMafellMinimaxMorsoNakahashiNarexOMAS ToolingOmecOsamaPizziRecord PowerReinboldSalvamac CrosscutsSarmaxSCM
SCM Available StockSedgwickStartriteStromabSuperficiTersa BladesTigerTec CNCTigra CarbideTranswaveTrend Router BitsVectric SoftwareVertongenVirutex ToolsWadkinWhitehillMorbidelli CNCCLEARANCE Manuals New In Brochures
Account
Settings
Currency
GBP - British Pound
AUD - Australian Dollar
CAD - Canadian Dollar
EUR - Euro
KES - Kenyan Shilling
Security & Privacy
For more information about our policy on cookies please visit this page
Who we are
Scott and Sargeant Woodworking Machinery Ltd
1 Blatchford Road, Horsham, West Sussex RH13 5QR
ENGLAND
Tel
+44 (0) 1403 273000
Registered Company in UK No 2448888
Scott and Sargeant Woodworking Machinery Ltd (“Scott and Sargeant”) are committed to complying with the General Data Protection Regulation and the Data Protection Act 2018, once enacted. Looking after the personal information you share with us is very important, and we want you to be confident that your personal data is kept safely and securely and to understand how we use it to offer you a better and more personalised shopping experience.
We have published this notice to help you understand
how and why Scott and Sargeant collect information from you;
who we share your information with, why and on what basis; and
what your rights are.
If we make changes to this notice we will notify you by updating it on our website. Scott and Sargeant will be what is known as the ‘Data Controller’ of the personal data you provide to us, and we will sometimes refer to ourselves in this notice as “we” or “us”. By Data Controller, this means Scott and Sargeant determines the purposes and way in which any personal data are, or will be, processed.
Should you need to contact us please write to: Data Protection Officer, Scott and Sargeant Woodworking Machinery Ltd, 1 Blatchford Road, Horsham, West Sussex, RH13 5QR, ENGLAND or via dataofficer@scosarg.co.uk quoting Security and Privacy Enquiry.
If you would like to request or review any part of your personal information held by Scott and Sargeant then fill out the contact form: https://www.scosarg.com/contact-us.
This privacy notice was last updated on 11th May 2018.
What information do we collect when you register and why?
When you buy goods from us, you are entering into a contract with us. You will need to set up a Scott and Sargeant Account before ordering from us, but you can also opt to checkout as a Guest, When placing an order we will ask you to provide some personal information such as;
Full name
Billing and delivery address
contact numbers, and
email address.
We do not store credit card details nor do we share customer financial details with any 3rd parties
In order to undertake website personalisation, we will also gather information about the devices you use to access our sites (desktop and mobile), and this may include IP address. For further information on our use of cookies and tracking please see our Cookie Notice.
In the course of running and maintaining our website we may also collect and process the following data:
Information about your use of our site, including pages viewed and the resources, links and PDFs you access. Such information includes traffic data, device data, location data and other communication data;
Information provided voluntarily by you. For example, your email address and contact details when you register to receive information; and
Information that you provide when you communicate with us via the Contact Form.
We may also collect and process the following data about you when providing services to you:
Personal information provided during the account opening process;
Information provided by you which relates to other individuals related to your account;
A record of any correspondence or communications between us; and
Details of transactions we carry out on your behalf.
We will also collect information using Cookies and please see our Cookie Policy for further details.
Under the GDPR Directive, we will ensure that your personal data is processed lawfully, fairly, and transparently, without adversely affecting your rights.
We will only process your personal data ; if at least one of the following basis applies:
you have given consent to the processing of your personal data for one or more specific purposes;
processing is necessary for the performance of a contract to which you are a party or in order to take steps at the request of you prior to entering into a contract;
processing is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which we are subject;
processing is necessary to protect the vital interests of you or of another natural person;
processing is necessary for the performance of a task carried out in the public interest or in the exercise of official authority vested in the controller; and/or
processing is necessary for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by us or by a third party such as our credit card payment processing, except where such interests are overridden by the fundamental rights and freedoms of the data subject which require protection of personal data, in particular where the data subject is a child.
How do we use your information?
Data Protection says that we are allowed to use and share your personal data only where we have a proper reason to do so. The law says we must have one or more of these reasons and these are:
Contract - your personal information is processed in order to fulfil a contractual arrangement e.g. in order to send you your order
Consent – where you agree to us using your information in this way e.g. for storing your payment card details.
Legitimate Interests - this means the interests of Scott and Sargeant in managing our business to allow us to provide you with the best products and service in the most secure and appropriate way e.g. to transfer your data to certain Third Party’s such as delivery partners.
Legal Obligation – where there is statutory or other legal requirement to share the information e.g. when we have to share your information for law enforcement purposes.
Here is a list of the ways that we may use your personal information, and which of the reasons described above we rely on to do so. Where we list legitimate interests as a reason, we also describe below what we believe these legitimate interests are.
What We Use Your Personal Information For
Our Reasons (Legal Basis)
Our Explanation Of Scott and Sargeant’s Legitimate Interests
Set up your Scott and Sargeant account
• Legitimate interest
Process efficiency in dealing with such activity.
Storing payment cards
• Consent
N/A
Process your orders
• Fulfilling a contract
Process efficiency in dealing with such activity.
Notify you of your order status.
• Legitimate interest
Process efficiency in dealing with such activity, and to make improvements to our services.
Manage your account/ provide customer services to you. This may include: customer services / communications activities call recording data verification customer complaints / queries
• Legal obligation/ Legitimate interests (depending on nature of services)
Keeping our records up to date, handling our customer contact efficiently and effectively, working out which of our products and services may interest you and telling you about them.
To detect, investigate and report financial crime (e.g. Fraud)
• Legal Obligation / legitimate interests
Developing and improving how we deal with financial crime. Complying with any legal obligation placed on us by regulators such as the FCA. Complying with any regulations that apply to us. Process efficiency in dealing with such activity, and to make service and process improvements.
Undertake website personalisation and administration.
• Legitimate interest
Developing products, services, applications and designs that attract and retain customers. Improving customer interaction with our sites. Defining types of customers for new products or services
Marketing communications to inform you of special offers, promotions, new lines and Sales. Provide you with online advertising.
• Legitimate interest
Developing products, services, applications and designs that attract and retain customers. Improving customer interaction with our sites.
Notifying you about enhancements to our services, such as changes to the website and new services that may be of interest to you.
• Legitimate interest
Developing products, services, applications and designs that attract and retain customers. Improving customer interaction with our sites.
Contact you to undertake customer satisfaction surveys, invite you to provide product reviews or for market research.
• Legitimate interest
Process efficiency in dealing with such activity.
Set up your Scott and Sargeant account
• Legitimate interest
Developing products, services, applications and designs that attract and retain customers. Improving customer interaction with our sites.
Maintaining network and data security
• Legitimate interest
To maintain the security of our network this in turns helps us to maintain the safety and confidentiality of your information.
Logistics planning, demand forecasting, management information and research
• Legitimate interest
We use information about shopping habits, products bought and volumes, to help us to respond to demand, ensure the right products get to the right areas and to help us plan our ranges.
We may also use information about you to:
To establish and administer accounts you set up with us and to fulfill the terms of any agreement you have with us;
Present site content effectively to you;
Provide information, products and services that you request, or (with your consent) which we think may interest you;
To notify you of any changes to our services, products;
Allow you to use our interactive services if you want to; and
Tell you our charges.
Provide data analysis for our management team.
If you are already our customer, we will only contact you electronically about products and service that pertain to your original investment.
If you are a new customer, you will only be contacted if you agree to it.
If you don’t want to be contacted for marketing purposes, please let us know.
In addition, if you don’t want us to use your personal data for any of the other reasons set out above, you can let us know at any time by contacting us at dataofficer@scosarg.co.uk , and we will delete your data from our systems. However, you acknowledge that doing so will limit our ability to provide the best possible services to you. In some cases, the collection of personal data may be a statutory or contractual requirement, and we will be limited in the services we can provide you if you don’t provide your personal data in these cases.
Where we store your data
Our servers and storage are based in the EEA in Ireland. In operating our website it may become necessary to transfer data that we collect from you to locations outside of the EEA for further processing and storing. By providing your personal data to us, you expressly consent to this transfer, processing or storing. This may involve the transfer of data by electronic means. Where your data is transferred outside of the UK, Scott and Sargeant
will ensure that the recipient agrees to keep your information confidential and hold it securely in accordance with the requirements of GDPR.
We use other sites including: Sagepay & Paypal for payment processing, Google for analytics and Mailchimp for maintaining our mailing lists.
We only keep your personal data for as long as we need to in order to use it as described above, and/or for as long as we have your permission to keep it. In any event, we will conduct an [annual] review to ascertain whether we need to keep your personal data. Your personal data will be deleted if we no longer need it.
Fraud prevention services
Before we provide services or goods we undertake checks for the purposes of preventing fraud and money laundering, and to verify your identity. These checks require us to process personal data about you.
The personal data you have provided, we have collected from you, or we have received from third parties will be used to prevent fraud and money laundering, and to verify your identity. Details of the personal information that will be processed include, for example: name, address, contact details, financial information, and device identifiers such as including IP address.
We and fraud prevention agencies may also enable law enforcement agencies to access and use your personal data to detect, investigate and prevent crime.
We process your personal data on the basis that we have a legitimate interest in preventing fraud and money laundering, and to verify identity, in order to protect our business and to comply with laws that apply to us. Such processing is also a contractual requirement of the services or financing you have requested.
We process your personal data on the basis that it is necessary in the public interest or in exercising official authority for us to prevent fraud and money laundering, and to verify identity, in order to protect ourselves and to comply with laws that apply to us.
Fraud prevention agencies can hold your personal data for different periods of time, and if you are considered to pose a fraud or money laundering risk, your data can be held for up to six years.
Automated Decisions
As part of the processing of your personal data, decisions may be made by automated means. This means we may automatically decide that you pose a fraud or money laundering risk if our processing reveals your behaviour to be consistent with money laundering or known fraudulent conduct, or is inconsistent with your previous submissions, or you appear to have deliberately hidden your true identity. You have rights in relation to automated decision-making: if you want to know more please contact us using the details above.
Consequences of Processing
If we, or a fraud prevention agency, determine that you pose a fraud or money laundering risk, we may refuse to provide the services or financing you have requested, or to employ you, or we may stop providing existing services to you. A record of any fraud or money laundering risk will be retained by the fraud prevention agencies, and may result in others refusing to provide services, financing or employment to you. If you have any questions about this, please contact us on the details above.
Data Transfers
Whenever fraud prevention agencies transfer your personal data outside of the European Economic Area, they impose contractual obligations on the recipients of that data to protect your personal data to the standard required in the European Economic Area. They may also require the recipient to subscribe to ‘international frameworks’ intended to enable secure data sharing.
Your Rights
Your personal data is protected by legal rights, which include your rights to object to our processing of your personal data; request that your personal data is erased or corrected; request access to your personal data. For more information or to exercise your data protection rights, please contact us using the contact details above. You also have a right to complain to the Information Commissioner’s Office, which regulates the processing of personal data.
Disclosing your information
We will not disclose your personal information to any other party, other than in accordance with this Privacy Policy and in the circumstances detailed below:
Where we are legally required by law to disclose your personal information.
To further fraud protection and reduce the risk of fraud.
Information security
We have in place procedures and controls to protect the personal data we collect from you from loss, misuse, unauthorised access, disclosure, alteration and destruction in accordance with GDPR.
You should protect access to your online account by keeping your username and a complex password private and ensuring you log off after using a shared computer.
Keeping in touch with you
We want to keep you up to date with information about new ranges, special offers and improvements to our website. When you set your account up, we will ask you if you want to receive this type of marketing information.
Scott and Sargeant will not share your information with companies outside of Scott and Sargeant Woodworking Machinery Ltd for their marketing purposes. If you decide you do not want to receive this marketing information you can request that we stop by using the unsubscribe link within the email which is the easiest way or contacting us by writing to Data Protection Officer, Scott and Sargeant Woodworking Machinery Ltd, 1 Blatchford Road, Horsham, West Sussex, RH13 5QR, ENGLAND or emailing us on dataofficer@scosarg.co.uk
quoting Security and Privacy Enquiry.
You may continue to receive mailings for a short period while your request is dealt with.
How long we keep your information
If we collect your personal information, the length of time we retain it is determined by a number of factors including the purpose for which we use that information and our obligations under other laws.
We may need your personal information to establish, bring or defend legal claims. For this purpose, we will always retain your personal information for 7 years after the date it is no longer needed by us for any of the purposes listed under How we use your information above. The only exceptions to this are where:
the law requires us to hold your personal information for a longer period, or delete it sooner;
you exercise your right to have the information erased (where it applies) and we do not need to hold it in connection with any of the reasons permitted or required under the law;
we bring or defend a legal claim or other proceedings during the period we retain your personal information, in which case we will retain your personal information until those proceedings have concluded and no further appeals are possible; or
in limited cases, existing or future law or a court or regulator requires us to keep your personal information for a longer or shorter period.
What are your rights
You are entitled to request the following from Scott and Sargeant, these are called your Data Subject Rights and there is more information on these on the Information Commissioners website www.ico.org.uk
Right of access –to request access to your personal information and information about how we process it
Right to rectification –to have your personal information corrected if it is inaccurate and to have incomplete personal information completed
Right to erasure (also known as the Right to be Forgotten)
Right to restriction of processing – to restrict processing of your personal information
Right to data portability - to electronically move, copy or transfer your personal information in a standard form
Right to object - to object to processing of your personal information
Rights with regards to automated individual decision making, including profiling –rights relating to automated decision making, including profiling
If you have any general questions about your rights or want to exercise your rights please contact dataofficer@scosarg.co.uk quoting Security and Privacy Enquiry.
You have the right to lodge a complaint with a data protection regulator in Europe, in particular in a country you work or live or where your legal rights have been infringed. The contact details for the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO), the data protection regulator in the UK, are available on the ICO website www.ico.org.uk where your personal information has or is being used in a way that you believe does not comply with data, however, we encourage you to contact us before making any complaint and we will seek to resolve any issues or concerns you may have.
Links to other sites
We operate links to third parties on this website but these links do not mean we endorse or approve that site’s policy towards visitor privacy. You should review their privacy policy before sending them any personal data. These sites include Sagepay & Paypal for payment processing transactions, google for analytics and Mailchimp for maintaining our mailing lists.
Quality of information
We till take all reasonable efforts to ensure that any personal information which we collect from you is accurate, up-to-date and complete.
If any of the information you have previously provided to us changes or is no longer accurate please notify us at gdpr@scosarg.co.uk
Changes
If we change our Privacy Policy, we will post the changes on this page. If we decide to, we may also email you.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you
If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to Scott and Sargeant Woodworking Machinery Ltd. 1 Blatchford Rd, Horsham, RH13 5QR, ENGLAND Company Registration Number: - 2448888.
Contact
Should you need to contact us please write to: Data Protection Officer, Scott and Sargeant Woodworking Machinery Ltd, 1 Blatchford Road, Horsham, West Sussex, RH13 5QR, ENGLAND or via dataofficer@scosarg.co.uk quoting Security and Privacy Enquiry.
If you would like to request or review any part of your personal information held by Scott and Sargeant then fill out the contact form: https://www.scosarg.com/contact-us
YouTube and Google Policies
We use YouTube API Services to show videos on this website.
YouTube terms of service are here: youtube.com/t/terms.
The relevant Google Privacy policies are here:
policies.google.com/privacy.
